https://eckberglammers.com/privacy-policy

Allison Rapp Fredrickson
Patrick Boley LL.M.
70 Acts Of Giving
Helping Small Businesses And Community Organizations Re-Build
Allison Rapp Fredrickson
Patrick Boley LL.M.
70 Acts of Giving
Helping Small Businesses and Community Organizations Re-Build
and GENERAL DISCLAIMER
GENERAL DISCLAIMEREckberg, Lammers, P.C. has prepared the materials and links on this website for informational purposes. The transmission and display of the information contained at, or accessed through these domains eckberglammers.com, hrcounsel.org is not intended to create—and receipt or viewing of it does not constitute an attorney-client relationship. Eckberg Lammers is not providing legal advice through this website, therefore you should not act upon any information you might receive from it without seeking professional counsel.
Eckberg Lammers welcomes the opportunity to consider having an Eckberg Lammer's attorney become your lawyer. If you are interested in possibly retaining us, we would be delighted to send you additional information about our qualifications, experience and standard terms of engagement. Please do not send us any confidential information without first speaking with one of our partners and receiving explicit authorization to send us the information.
The materials on this website are intended, but not guaranteed, to reflect current legal developments and the current state of the law. Eckberg Lammers does not, however, represent, warrant, or guarantee we will be complete, accurate, or up to date when you view them. Eckberg Lammers is not responsible for any third-party content that may be accessed through this website. Any reference to third-party information, products, or services linked to this website does not constitute an expressed or implied endorsement by Eckberg Lammers.
This website is not intended to constitute advertising. Under the applicable laws, regulations, and ethical rules of some jurisdictions, however, the contents of this website might be deemed to constitute advertising. We do not wish to represent anyone desiring representation based upon viewing this website in one of those jurisdictions.
PRIVACY POLICYUpdated: January 1st, 2019This Privacy Policy governs the collection, disclosure and use of personal information and data relating to potential and existing users of the services ("you") of Eckberg Lammers, P.C. This Privacy Policy provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information, and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.
The Website(s) are operated by Eckberg Lammers, P.C.
We are committed to your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
Please read this policy carefully as it explains the personal information we collect about you and how such personal information is handled. By your continued use of our services (including our websites), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you must not use our products or services. Please check back for updates regularly, as we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.
If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use your personal information, please contact us by email at contact@eckberglammers.com or write to us at the following address:
1809 Northwestern Avenue
Stillwater, MN 55082
TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED
The following are the types of information we may collect:
Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or fax number, demographic information, such as your date of birth, age, gender, occupation, financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information, if payments are required.
Your name;
Company Name;
Payment processing information;
Company or business postal address;
Company or business email address;
Business landline or mobile telephone number;
Your job title or job role
Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website(s), such as your click-stream data and your IP address.
See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.
Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.
The personal information that we may collect about you broadly falls into the following categories:
HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED
We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below.
COOKIES:
As with many Websites, our Websites use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a unique, random number that is stored in the browser on your computer. The cookie doesn't identify you, just the computer that is used to visit the site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit our website and where visitors go on the site. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the website. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Cookies are not tied to personal information.
Third Party Cookies
The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.
Change Google data sharing options
LinkedIn Privacy Policy
Facebook Data Policy
Constant Contact Privacy Policy
ANALYTICS & REMARKETING
If you use our websites, we may collect information about you or your computer when you browse to allow you to use the services available and collect anonymous information about you or your computer for analysis to support continual improvements to our website and services.
Information collected:
Time on site
Pages Visited
Depth of Scroll
Device used
EMAIL NEWSLETTERS
We use Constant Contact to create and manage email newsletters, case law updates, seminar invitations and other client and partner notifications.
Information Used and Collected:
Name
Email Address
Company Name
SEMINAR / TRAINING SESSION REGISTRATIONS
We offer informational seminars and developmental training classes and require registrants to provide personal information to manage those sessions.
Information collected:
Name
Company
Phone Number
Email Address
Payment Method (no credit card information is stored), if any payment is required
HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use the personal information that we collect about you to respond to requests for information, your meeting scheduling requests with our firm, payment collection and processing, and for the provision of our services to you or to the company that you represent, and for providing continuing support. We also process your personal information where we are required to do so by law, and for the exercise or defense of legal claims.
From time to time, we may contact you for research purposes, or to tell you about our seminar and training session offers and other services. Where appropriate, we will obtain your consent to do so. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any of those communications.
If we intend on using your personal information for any other purpose, we will let you know how we intend to use it when it is captured.
We will only process your personal information for the specific purposes listed above or for any other purposes specifically permitted by law. Your personal information will only be processed to the extent that it is necessary for the specific purposes listed above.
Our legal basis for processing your personal information
We will only process your personal information where you have consented (which you may withdraw after giving it if we are relying on consent as a legal basis), in order to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others, for example, for market research purposes or, where you are an existing customer or user, to promote firm and services.
How long we retain your personal information
We will only retain personal information if it is required for a specific purpose. We have a statutory duty to keep certain records for a specified minimum period, for example personal information in relation to the service for which you are using Eckberg Lammers, P.C. We will not retain any data that is not connected to the service for longer than [5 years]. We will also retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Information that is no longer required for any valid business purpose, and that we are not required to keep pursuant to any applicable law, will be routinely destroyed by secure means.
We may share your personal information with the following categories of recipients:
Our law firm [company], third party services providers and partners who provide data processing services to us (for example, to support the delivery of, provide functionality on, or help to enhance the security of our Website), or who otherwise process personal information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Notice or notified to you when we collect your personal information.
Any competent law enforcement body, regulatory, government agency, court or other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary (i) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (ii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, or (iii) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person;
A potential buyer (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any proposed purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Notice;
Any other person with your consent to the disclosure.
How we protect your information
We use reasonable and appropriate administrative, technical, and organizational measures to safeguard personal information against loss, theft and unauthorized uses, access, disclosure, modifications or destruction. Certain areas of our websites may be password protected. If you are a user of our websites and have a password, you can help to preserve your privacy by ensuring that you do not share your password with anyone else.
Choices you have about how we use your information
You have the following rights under data protection laws:
If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below.
In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below.
You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we may send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in the marketing e-mails or newsletters we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing (such as postal marketing or telemarketing), then please contact us using the contact details provided under the "How to contact us" heading below.
Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.
These rights may not apply in some cases, including where we must comply with legal requirements, where it would violate the rights of someone other than the individual requesting access, or (in the case of your right to request access to your personal information) where the request is manifestly unfounded or excessive.
If you would like to request access to, correction, amendment, or deletion of your personal information, please contact us using one of the methods below. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity. In certain circumstances, for instance if you request substantial copies of documents, we may charge a reasonable fee.
We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make. We will obtain your consent to any material changes if and where this is required by applicable data protection laws.
You can see when this Privacy Policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this document.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have a concern or complaint about privacy, confidentiality or the personal information handling practices of Eckberg Lammers, P.C., our employees or service suppliers, please contact:
Eckberg Lammers, P.C.
1809 Northwestern Avenue
Stillwater, MN 55082
USA
651-439-2878
contact@eckberglammers.com
WEBSITES GOVERNED BY THIS POLICY
eckberglammers.com
hrcounsel.org
This site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to assist with navigation and your ability to provide feedback, analyze your use of our website, and assist with our promotional and marketing efforts. Read our Privacy Policy for more information.
Accept
